http://www.suu.edu/privacy/

Skip to main content
Privacy Statement
Southern Utah University has created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. This document explains how we gather, use, and protect your information.
We Don't Sell Your Contact Information
While using this site, you may choose to submit personal information through email or online forms. We will use this information to process your requests. We will not intentionally sell, share, or distribute your personal information to third parties, except as required by law or University policy.
Statistical Logs Kept
SUU uses programs to collect data about visitor traffic to our site. We do not attempt to personally identify visitors. Instead we collect data to analyze in aggregate to determine trends and improve our sites. Here are some examples of the types of data we routinely collect:
Internet address of computer
Browser type
Device type
Referring web page
Date, time & duration of visit
Cookies Used to Preserve Data
Internal search terms
Cookies
Most websites use cookies. A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, display preferences) either during a single session or over a period of time, so you don't have to keep re-entering information during a session or whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. For instance, the mySUU portal uses cookies (active only during your session) to remember password and menu settings. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can turn them off in your browser or set your browser to ask you before accepting new cookies although this may affect functionality. Cookie information is not used to identify you personally.
Security Programs Running
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, to assist in maintaining data security, and to assist in correctly using the information we collect online. We do not intentionally release personal information gleaned from these programs to others, except as required by law.
Security Precautions You Should Take
Although we make every effort to secure our networks, the University cannot guarantee privacy of online communications. Use discretion in providing information in online classes, chatrooms, or other open forums on the Web. If you use mySUU to access personal records, be sure to "lock up" when you leave by exiting the site AND closing your browser. Otherwise, the next person to use the computer may see your information.
Alternate Ways to Submit Information
You have a choice about whether to provide personal information online. For other options, contact the department associated with the form being completed to learn how you can provide information by phone, mail, fax or in person.
Other Sites Have Different Policies
This site contains links to other independently managed sites. Some may use information for purposes other than stated above; be sure to read their separate privacy statements. University sites also contain links to sites outside SUU; these sites may have their own privacy statement -- or none at all. We urge you to exercise caution when providing personal data to any site. Check their policies and contact them if you have questions.
Protecting Children's Privacy
We encourage parents to explore our website with their children. If we learn that a child under age 13 has provided personally identifiable information to our sites, we will promptly remove this from our files. For more on children's privacy rights, read about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act at the FTC's website.
Changing Your Information
Here's how to review or change your personal profile information (address, home phone, e-mail):
On the Web – Log into mySUU and visit your profile
In Person – Visit the Registrar’s Office in the Sharwan Smith Center or the Alumni Office
